That would be a correct
plot for that question.
So does everybody see?
I just want you to get
a feeling for this plot.
We introduced it
Monday, and I really
want you to feel your
oneness with this plot
because it's a
very important plot
to understand why glasses form.
All right, now
moving on, there's
a lot of properties of
glasses, and here I'm
talking about oxide
glasses, so silica.
Remember, silicon oxide,
oxide, silica, alumina.
These are, oh, oxide.
We talked about that.
Chemically inert,
electrically insulating,
mechanically brittle,
optically transparent,
visually arresting--
I like that one--
these are the
properties that we know
about these kinds of glasses.
We already know them.
But what I want to
talk about today
is how they can be engineered.
And this plot is a basis
for understanding that.
And so is spaghetti, and that's
what we're going to talk about.
So the very first one--
which we'll set up
our demo in just a few minutes.
The very first one that
I want to talk about
is the mechanical properties.
We know glass to
be very brittle,
but could we change its
mechanical properties?
Could we do something about
the mechanical properties?
And by the way, if those
are the things that
dictate whether a
glass forms or not,
then those are the
things that you
might think we might try to
engineer if we want to change
the properties of glass.